PHONE : +66 094 052 8596

EMAIL: Wasinmekkit@gmail.com

ADDRESS: 230/6405 Chaengwattana Rd. Laksi Area,

Bangkok, Thailand, 10210





Front End Developer & Digital Channel Specialist

### Visit My Portfolio Website



https://bit.lv/wasin-mekk

## **PROFILE**

With 5<sup>th</sup> years of experience in web development and design, I am a creative and versatile Front End Developer. Using HTML, CSS, SCSS, Javascript, and modern libraries and frameworks are all required. Proficient in UI/UX design and motion graphics. Digital marketing, Experience Management, Programmatic Advertising, and Search engine optimization are all areas in which I am knowledgeable and passionate.

## **EXPERTISE**

- · Website Development
- UX/UI Design
- · Graphic Design
- Motion Graphic
- Animation
- Search engine optimization
- · Digital Marketing
- · Serverless Computing
- Programmatic Advertising

## **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2017

### Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology

North Bangkok University

2012 - 2015

# Diploma Vocational Certificate in Information Technology

Siam Business Administration Technological College

## REFERENCE

### Mr. Paisan Sa-nguansin

Web Management and Monetization Manager **Advanced Info Service PLC.** Paisansa@ais.co.th

#### Mr. Anucha Sanu

Senior Web Developer
North Bangkok University
Anucha.sa@northbkk.ac.th

## Experience

2018 - Present

### Front End Developer & Digital Channel Specialist | Advanced Info Service PLC.

Working as a Front End Developer & Digital Channel Specialist. I created a variety of websites for businesses in the telecommunications industry using HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, and Adobe AEM as DXP. I contributed to the company's developer experience by implementing tools and technologies to improve our development process. And contributed with my team to improve UX/UI design to increase the efficiency of the customer journey. In addition, website optimization, Digital Experience Platforms and Programmatic Advertising Platforms such as Cloudflare worker, Adobe DTM, Adobe Analytics, Adnuntius, Relay42, and Cxense.

2017 - 2018

### Web Developer & Public Relations Specialist | North Bangkok University

As a Web Developer and Public Relations Specialist. I contributed to the development of the university website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL, and WordPress as CMS. To improve online sales and enhance university website traffic, including the creation of advertising material such as motion graphics, banners, posters, Google Ads, and social media ads.

2016 - 2017

## Software Technician | ICOM TECH CO.,LTD

My primary responsibility as a Software Technician was to support and advise clients. In terms of software applications as well as problem-solving. This includes software installation and client training. In addition, technical and manual preparation support and consultation to the sales team.

## **AWARDS**

202

### **Honorable Mention award**

Animation@Work 2020 from Reallusion.

201

### **Glare Outstanding Work**

Asiagraph Reallusion Animation Award From Asiagraph.

2017

### First Runner-up award

Toyota moving challenge Animation Contest.

2015

### Winner Award and Popular vote

Thailand Animation Contest From NECTEC.